// Flange and Bucket

// Currently can't have form and show_answers set to false at the same time

const publish_answers = [true, true, true, true, true, false, false];

/* eslint-disable no-unused-vars */
const blankRound = [
  {
    title: '',
    date: '',
    deadline: '',
    show_answers: false,
    form: true,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[1],
    questions: [
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
    ],
  },
];

const rounds = [
  {
    title: '8. Famous Andrews – Well Sort Of',
    date: '2020/03/30',
    deadline: '2020/03/31 20:00',
    show_answers: false,
    form: true,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[6],
    questions: [
      { question: 'Prince who might have been a naughty boy', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Too good to hurry tennis player', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Musical victim of Morecombe and Wise', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Double barrelled composer of musicals', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Sang with sweaters', answer: '' },
      { question: 'He topped the “Andy” poll and was the 7th US President', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Sunday interviewer who’s all ears', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Not of Casterbridge,but Greater Manchester', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Aka Freddie', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Soup can artist', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Industrialist, philanthropist and founder of over 200 libraries and learning institutions worldwide', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Composer of Waltzing Matilda', answer: '' },
      { question: 'His life was your life', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Heavyweight political pundit who frightened Boris', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Grand slam tennis player married to Steffi Graf', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Patron saint of Scotland', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Canadian born British Conservative Prime minister from 1922 to 1923 aka “unknownPM”', answer: '' },
      { question: 'British 2012 and 2014 superhero Actor', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Blindingly brilliant classical crossover singer', answer: '' },
      { question: 'Brought the hills to life', answer: '' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '7. Nursery Rhymes',
    date: '2020/03/30',
    deadline: '2020/03/31 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[6],
    questions: [
      { question: 'How many blind mice were there?', answer: 'Three' },
      { question: 'What did nimble jack jump over?', answer: 'A candle stick' },
      { question: 'What was the queen eating in her parlour?', answer: 'Bread and honey' },
      { question: 'Why was the old man thrown down the stairs?', answer: `Because he wouldn't say his prayers` },
      {
        question: 'What was the colour of the owl’s and the pussy cat’s boat',
        answer: 'Pea green',
      },
      { question: 'To where would you ride a cock horse?', answer: 'Banbury Cross' },
      { question: 'Who lost her sheep?', answer: 'Little Bo Peep' },
      {
        question: 'What would give to your sons if you had no daughters?',
        answer: 'Hot cross buns',
      },
      { question: 'Who came tumbling after?', answer: 'Jill' },
      {
        question:
          'What was Wee Willy Winkie wearing when he ran through the street?',
        answer: 'Nightgown',
      },
      { question: 'Who came to see the nut tree?', answer: `The king of Spain's daugher` },
      {
        question: 'For how long had the Pease pudding been in the pot?',
        answer: 'Nine days',
      },
      { question: 'Who is going to pay up when rich?', answer: 'The bells of Shoreditch' },
      { question: 'From what did Jack pull the plum?', answer: 'A Christmas pie' },
      { question: 'Who found the pocket?', answer: 'Kitty Fisher' },
      { question: 'Who could eat no lean?', answer: `Jack Spratt's wife` },
      { question: 'Who was warming her pretty little toes?', answer: 'Litte Polly Flinders' },
      { question: 'Which ladybird escaped the conflagration?', answer: 'Ann' },
      { question: 'Who said to whom tomorrow will be Monday?', answer: 'Tommy Snooks to Bessy Brooks' },
      { question: 'Who did puss look at in London?', answer: 'The Queen' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '6. Chocolates',
    date: '2020/03/28',
    deadline: '2020/03/29 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[5],
    questions: [
      { question: 'Regent or Bond? (7,6)', answer: 'Quality Street' },
      { question: 'Not very practical (4,4)', answer: 'Milk Tray' },
      { question: 'Birthdays, Anniversaries (12)', answer: 'Celebrations' },
      { question: 'Witchcraft (5,5)', answer: 'Black Magic' },
      { question: 'William Tell, V.Cs, Spiderman (6)', answer: 'Heroes' },
      { question: 'Peace, Rambling Rector, Judi Dench (5)', answer: 'Roses' },
      { question: 'Big Bus (6,6)', answer: 'Double Decker' },
      { question: 'University Challenge panellists (8)', answer: 'Smarties' },
      { question: 'It’s not Dad’s (4)', answer: `Mars (get it? Mar's)` },
      { question: 'An off-white pub (5,3)', answer: 'Milky Bar' },
      { question: 'Sh! (5)', answer: 'Wispa' },
      { question: 'A feline uniform (3,3)', answer: 'Kit Kat' },
      { question: 'Outlaw (6)', answer: 'Bandit' },
      { question: 'Travelling musicians (9)', answer: 'Minstrels' },
      { question: 'Reward for Capturing (6)', answer: 'Bounty' },
      { question: 'Whisky taunters (9)', answer: 'Malteasers' },
      { question: 'Joy in Istanbul (7,7)', answer: 'Turkish Delight' },
      { question: 'Theme (5)', answer: 'Topic' },
      { question: 'A noisy stretch of water (5)', answer: 'Flake' },
      { question: '10 Cents (4) or (4,3)', answer: 'Daim (Bar)' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: `5. Who's line is it anyway?`,
    date: '2020/03/27',
    deadline: '2020/03/27 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[4],
    questions: [
      { question: 'A hand bag', answer: 'Lady Bracknell' },
      {
        question: 'Frankly my dear I don’t give a damn!',
        answer: 'Rhett Butler',
      },
      {
        question: 'I believe it is peace for our time',
        answer: 'Neville Chamberlain',
      },
      { question: 'To infinity and beyond', answer: 'Buzz Lightyear' },
      {
        question: 'Never has so much, been owed by so many, to so few.',
        answer: 'Winston Churchill',
      },
      {
        question:
          'I’m playing all ofthe notes but not necessarily in the right order',
        answer: 'Eric Morecombe',
      },
      { question: 'Four Candles', answer: 'Two Ronnies' },
      {
        question: 'To be or not to be: that is the question?',
        answer: 'Hamlet',
      },
      {
        question: 'Stop throwing those bloody spears at me.',
        answer: 'Peachy Carnehan (Michael Caine)',
      },
      {
        question: 'That’s one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind',
        answer: 'Neil Armstrong',
      },
      { question: 'The lady’s not for turning', answer: 'Margeret Thatcher' },
      {
        question: 'Kiss me harder or was it Kismet Hardy.',
        answer: 'Horatio Nelson',
      },
      { question: 'I am your father', answer: 'Darth Vader' },
      {
        question: 'Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee',
        answer: 'Mohamed Ali',
      },
      { question: 'I have a dream', answer: 'Dr Martin Luther King' },
      { question: 'Good moaning', answer: 'Officer Crabtree (Arthur Bostrom)' },
      {
        question: 'We’re going to be in the Hudson',
        answer: 'Chesley "Sully" Sullenberger',
      },
      { question: 'You stupid boy!', answer: 'Captain Mainwaring' },
      {
        question: 'Nice to see you, to see you nice',
        answer: 'Bruce Forsythe',
      },
      {
        question: 'Life is what happens when you are busy making other plans',
        answer: 'John Lennon',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '4. Towns and Cities',
    date: '2020/03/26',
    deadline: '2020/03/26 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[3],
    questions: [
      { question: 'Tub full of water', answer: 'Bath' },
      { question: 'Professor of rollers', answer: 'Doncaster' },
      { question: 'Witches attempt to meet', answer: 'Coventry' },
      { question: 'A Person who is leaving', answer: 'Exeter' },
      { question: 'People Rock', answer: 'Folkstone' },
      { question: 'A complete bacon', answer: 'Fulham' },
      { question: 'Ship’s men', answer: 'Crewe' },
      { question: 'Tying Meat', answer: 'Nottingham' },
      { question: 'Latest Fortified Wine', answer: 'Newport' },
      { question: 'Religious Skull', answer: 'Holyhead' },
      { question: 'Detective clues', answer: 'Leeds' },
      { question: 'Sounds like Piggot’s town', answer: 'Leicester' },
      {
        question: 'Where cattle cross the river',
        answer: 'Oxbridge or Cowbridge',
      },
      { question: 'Almost speechless in front of chips', answer: 'Dumfries' },
      { question: 'Mothers entrance', answer: 'Margate' },
      { question: 'USA President', answer: 'Licoln or Washington' },
      { question: 'Chocolate bar without that is', answer: 'York' },
      { question: 'Fake First Lady', answer: 'Evesham' },
      { question: 'Rifle', answer: 'Winchester or Enfield' },
      { question: 'Cook al fresco', answer: 'Sheffield' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '3. Sleuth Creators',
    date: '2020/03/25',
    deadline: '2020/03/26 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[2],
    questions: [
      { question: 'Morse', answer: 'Colin Dexter' },
      { question: 'Frost', answer: 'R D Wingfield' },
      { question: 'Wexford', answer: 'Ruth Rendell' },
      { question: 'Poirot', answer: 'Agatha Christie' },
      { question: 'Foyle', answer: 'Anthony Horowitz' },
      { question: 'Colombo', answer: 'William Link and Richard Levinson' },
      { question: 'Inspector Rebus', answer: 'Ian Rankin' },
      { question: 'Maigret', answer: 'George Simenon' },
      { question: 'Harry Hole', answer: 'Jo Nesbo' },
      { question: 'Sherlock Holmes', answer: 'Sir Arthur Conan Doyle' },
      { question: 'Brother Cadfel', answer: 'Ellis Peters' },
      { question: 'Miss Marple', answer: 'Agatha Christie' },
      { question: 'Philip Marlowe', answer: 'Raymond Chandler' },
      { question: 'Lord Peter Wimsey', answer: 'Dorothy L Sayers' },
      { question: 'Jack Reacher', answer: 'Lee Child' },
      { question: 'Perry Mason', answer: 'Erle Stanley Gardner' },
      { question: 'Hieronymus “Harry” Bosch', answer: 'Michael Connely' },
      { question: 'Dick Tracy', answer: 'Chester Gould' },
      { question: 'Seeley Booth (Bones)', answer: 'Kathy Riechs' },
      { question: 'Adam Dalgleish', answer: 'P D James' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '2. Initial Numbers',
    date: '2020/03/24',
    deadline: '2020/03/25 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[1],
    questions: [
      { question: '1 W on a U', answer: '1 Wheel on a Unicycle' },
      { question: '3 BM', answer: '3 Blind Mice' },
      { question: '4 S in a Y', answer: '4 Seasons in a Year' },
      { question: '6 S of a C', answer: '6 Sides of a Cube' },
      { question: '7 W of the W', answer: '7 Wonders of the World' },
      { question: '8 is TC', answer: '8 is two cubed' },
      { question: '11 P in a FT', answer: '11 Players in a Football Team' },
      { question: '12 S of the Z', answer: '12 Signs of the Zodiac' },
      { question: '13 in a BD', answer: '13 in a Bakers Dozen' },
      { question: '16 O in a P', answer: '16 Ounces in a Pound ' },
      {
        question: '24 B B in a P',
        answer: '4 and 20 Blackbirds baked in a Pie',
      },
      {
        question: '29 D in F in a LY',
        answer: '29 Days in February in a Leap Year',
      },
      {
        question: '32 DF at which WF',
        answer: '32 Degrees Fahrenheit at which Water Freezes',
      },
      { question: '57 HV', answer: '57 Heinz Varieties' },
      { question: '64 S on a CB', answer: '64 Squares on a Chess Board' },
      { question: '76 T in the BP', answer: '76 Trombones in the Big Parade' },
      { question: '99 RB', answer: '99 Red Balloons' },
      { question: '101 D', answer: '101 Dalmatians' },
      { question: '1760 Y in a M', answer: '1760 Yards in a Mile' },
      { question: '9,000,000 B in B', answer: '9 Million Bicycles in Beijing' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '1. Musicals',
    date: '2020/03/22',
    deadline: '2020/03/24 - 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    published: true,
    form: false,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[0],
    questions: [
      { question: 'The shrew tamed? (4, 2, 4)', answer: 'Kiss me Kate' },
      {
        question: 'Spectre in singing event? (3, 7, 2, 3, 5)',
        answer: 'The Phantom of the Opera',
      },
      {
        question: '_____ Lennox or _____ get your gun or _____ Oakley? (5)',
        answer: 'Annie',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Enough wives for everybody - well at least one each? (5, 6, 3, 5, 8)',
        answer: 'Seven Brides for Seven Brothers',
      },
      { question: 'East enders Flying Squad? (7, 4)', answer: 'Sweeney Todd' },
      { question: 'Notoriety? (4)', answer: 'Fame' },
      { question: 'World champion racing car driver? (8)', answer: 'Hamilton' },
      { question: 'US State? (8)', answer: 'Oklahoma' },
      {
        question: 'Royal Siamese governess makes good? (3, 4, 3, 1)',
        answer: 'The King and I',
      },
      {
        question: 'Did Maria bring the hills to life? (3, 5, 2, 5)',
        answer: 'The Sound of Music',
      },
      { question: 'Greetings child’s toy? (5, 5)', answer: 'Hello Dolly' },
      { question: 'Threepence? (4, 1, 8)', answer: 'Half a Sixpence' },
      {
        question: 'Not a tale from the orient? (4, 4, 5)',
        answer: 'West Side Story',
      },
      { question: 'William Writer? (5, 6)', answer: 'Billy Elliot' },
      { question: 'The French poor ones? (3, 10)', answer: 'Les Misérables' },
      {
        question: 'Opposite of North Atlantic? (5, 7)',
        answer: 'South Pacific',
      },
      {
        question: 'Not your dark gentleman? (2, 4, 4)',
        answer: 'My Fair Lady',
      },
      { question: 'Mother Farrow? (5, 3)', answer: 'Mamma Mia' },
      { question: 'Not dogs? (4)', answer: 'Cats' },
      {
        question: 'Night-time features fast train? (9,7)',
        answer: 'Starlight Express',
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default rounds;
